+32 56 84 34 14 [info@paris-elysees.com](mailto:info@paris-elysees.com)

**Total:** 0,00€

* * *

No products in the cart.

Select Page

#### Paris Elysees Perfumes & Beauty

_Global Distribution_  
Calle Gran de Gracia 15 / 3 / 2, 08012 Barcelone, Espagne.

#### Laboratoires Paris Elysees

_Logistic Europe_  
+32 56 84 34 14  
info@paris-elysees.com

You can also get in touch with us via our [Contact Form](https://paris-elysees.com/homepage/contact-paris-elysees/ "Contact Paris Elysees using our Contact Form")

[P.E. Classics  
Collection](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/women-fragrances/classics/ "P.E. Classics Collection of Fragrances for Women")

[Billion Woman Night NEW!](https://paris-elysees.com/product/billion-woman-night/ "Billion Woman Night Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")  
[Sexy Woman Love NEW!](https://paris-elysees.com/product/sexy-woman-love/ "Sexy Woman Love Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")  
[Blue Melody NEW!](https://paris-elysees.com/product/blue-melody/ "Blue Melody Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")  
[Billion Woman](https://paris-elysees.com/product/billion-woman/ "Billion Woman Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")  
[Billion Woman Love](https://paris-elysees.com/product/billion-woman-love/ "Billion Woman Love Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")

[Vodka Feminine  
Collection](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/women-fragrances/vodka-women/ "Vodka Feminine Collection of Fragrances for Women")

[Vodka Love](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-love/ "Vodka Love Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")

[Romantic  
Collection](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/women-fragrances/romantic/ "Romantic Collection of Fragrances for Women")

[Romantic Dream](https://paris-elysees.com/product/romantic-dream/ "Romantic Dream Eau de Parfum 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")  
[Romantic Glamour](https://paris-elysees.com/product/romantic-glamour/ "Romantic Glamour Eau de Parfum 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")  
[Romantic Night](https://paris-elysees.com/product/romantic-night/ "Romantic Night Eau de Parfum 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Women")

[Billion Dollar  
Collection](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/men-fragrances/billion-dollar/ "Billion Dollar Collection of Fragrances for Men")

[Billion Dollar Night NEW!](https://paris-elysees.com/product/billion-dollar-night/ "Billion Dollar Night Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Billion Dollar](https://paris-elysees.com/product/billion-dollar/ "Billion Dollar Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Billion Dollar Casino Royal](https://paris-elysees.com/product/billion-dollar-casino-royal/ "Billion Dollar Casino Royal Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")

[Caviar  
Collection](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/men-fragrances/caviar/ "Caviar Collection of Fragrances for Men")

[Caviar Night NEW!](https://paris-elysees.com/product/caviar-night/ "Caviar Night Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Caviar Amber](https://paris-elysees.com/product/caviar-amber/ "Caviar Amber Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Caviar Black](https://paris-elysees.com/product/caviar-black/ "Caviar Black Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")

[Vodka Masculine  
Collection](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/men-fragrances/vodka-men/ "Vodka Masculine Collection of Fragrances for Men")

[Vodka Wild NEW!](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-wild/ "Vodka Wild Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Vodka Diamond](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-diamond/ "Vodka Diamond Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Vodka Extreme](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-extreme/ "Vodka Extreme Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Vodka Limited Edition](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-limited-edition/ "Vodka Limited Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Vodka Man](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-man/ "Vodka Man Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")  
[Vodka Night](https://paris-elysees.com/product/vodka-night/ "Vodka Night Eau de Toilette 100ml (3.3 fl.oz) for Men")

Paris Elysees [Homepage](https://paris-elysees.com/) > [Legal Notice](https://paris-elysees.com/homepage/legal-notice/) > Privacy Policy

##### table of content

1. [Data Protection Officer](#datacontrol "How we protect your data")
2. [Type of data](#datatype "Type of data we collect")
3. [Use of Cookies](#cookie1 "How and why we use cookies")
4. [Use of Log files](#logs "How we use log files")
5. [Type of Cookies](#cookie2 "What type of cookies we use")
6. [Contact Us](#form "How to contact Paris Elysees Parfums")
7. [Newsletters subscription](#newsletter "Inscription to receive our newsletter")
8. [Disclosure to 3rd parties](#disclosure "Disclosure to 3rd parties")
9. [Automation Processes](#adm "Automated Decision Making")
10. [Use of Profiling](#profile "How we use profiling")
11. [3rd parties Data processing](#thirdparties "Data processing by 3rd parties")
12. [Use of Social Media](#social "How we use social media")
13. [Use of Plug Ins](#plugins "What plug ins we use and why")
14. [Your Rights on your Data](#yourrights "Your rights over your data")
15. [Website Security mesures](#security "What we do for your safety")
16. [Modifications](#changes "Modifications of this privacy policy")
17. [Disputes Settlement](#disputes "Online Settlement of Disputes")
18. [GTS](#gts "General Terms & Conditions")

PRIVACY POLICY & DATA USE
=========================

This page explains what data we collect and how we use it on paris-elysees.com.  
Please read it in order to know your rights and how to exercise them.

We are pleased that you have visited our website and are interested in our company and our products. The protection of your data and information is an issue that we take seriously and we therefore want you to feel safe when you visit our website. The section below provides, in accordance with applicable data privacy regulations, information about the personal data we collect when you:

visit our website: paris-elysees.com,  
subscribe to Paris Elysees Parfums email newsletters.

(hereinafter collectively called “website”), for what purposes we use and how we utilise such data to optimise our services for you.

1\. CONTROLLER, DATA PROTECTION OFFICER OF THE CONTROLLER
---------------------------------------------------------

(1) Controller according to Art. 4 (7) of EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is

**Paris Elysees Perfume and Beauty SL.  
Calle Gran de Gracia 15 / 3 / 2,  
08012 Barcelona, Spain.  
Phone in Belgium (showroom & logistics): +32 56 84 34 14  
e-mail: [privacy@paris-elysees.com](mailto:privacy@paris-elysees.com "Send an email to privacy@paris-elysees.com")**

hereinafter referred to with “Paris Elysees”, “Paris Elysees Perfume”, “Paris Elysees Parfums”, “PEPB”, “we” or “us”.  
For more information about the vendor, refer to our [Legal Notice](https://paris-elysees.com/homepage/legal-notice/ "Visit Paris Elysees Parfums Legal Notice") .

(2) The data security officer can be reached at: [privacy@paris-elysees.com](mailto:privacy@paris-elysees.com "Send an email to privacy@paris-elysees.com") or by using the aforementioned postal address with attention to Data security officer (DPO).

2\. TYPES OF DATA PROCESSED, DATA SUBJECT CATEGORIES
----------------------------------------------------

### 2.1 TYPE OF DATA PROCESSED

Usage data (e.g., visited sites, interest in contents, access times)  
Meta /communications data (e.g., device information, IP addresses)

### 2.2 DATA SUBJECT CATEGORIES

Visitors and users of the website  
Interested parties and business partners  
Newsletter subscribers  
(The aforementioned persons are collectively referred to below as “User”.)

### 2.3 DATA RETENTION

We store the following data for the period of time required by law and the data is automatically deleted at the end of this period.  
Inactive Accounts: 3 months,  
Pending Orders: 1 month,  
Failed Orders: 1 month,  
Canceled Orders: 1 month,  
Completed Orders: 24 month.  
You may request that your data be deleted from our databases at any time by contacting the DPO at the address indicated in point 1. of this Privacy Policy.

3\. USE OF COOKIES
------------------

We use your personal data to provide our website, its functions and contents.

to identify you as a contractual partner.  
to respond to contact requests and communicate with Users.  
to assert, enforce, maintain or defend against any legal claim(s) and legal dispute(s) as well as identify, investigate and prevent any criminal acts  
for security measures  
to assess coverage  
for the purpose of direct marketing, e.g. in the form of an e-mail newsletter or postal advertising.  
for the purpose of surveys of product and service satisfaction and the analysis of these surveys.

4\. PROVISION OF WEBSITE AND LOGFILES
-------------------------------------

(1) In case of using the website only for information purposes, i.e. when you are not registered or otherwise provide us with information, we collect only personal data that your browser automatically sends to our server. If you want to browse our website, we collect the following data which are technically necessary for us to show you our website and ensure its stability and security (this is legally permitted under Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) f) of GDPR):

IP address  
Date and time of inquiry  
Time zone difference to Greenwich Mean Time (GMT)  
Content of request (specific page)  
Access status/HTTP status code  
Amount of data transmitted respectively  
Website, from which the request comes  
Browser  
Operating system and its interface  
Language and version of browser software

(2) User IP addresses are deleted or anonymised after the end of website use. In the case of anonymisation, the IP addresses are changed in such a way that the individual details relating to personal or factual circumstances can no longer be assigned to a specific or identifiable natural person or can only be assigned subject to a disproportionate amount of time, cost and effort.

5\. COOKIES
-----------

(1) In addition to the aforementioned logfile data, cookies are saved on your computer when you use our website. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your hard drive and assigned to your browser and which provide certain information to the entity setting the cookie (us in this case). Cookies cannot cause programs to run nor transmit viruses to your computer. They are used to make our internet offering more user-friendly and effective on a whole.

(2) Use of cookies:  
a) This website uses the following types of cookies, whose scope and functions are explained below:

Session cookies (see b)  
Permanent cookies (see c).

b) Session cookies store a so-called session ID, with which different requests from your browser can be assigned to the shared session. Session cookies are deleted when you log out or close your browser. If you launch your browser again and return to the website, the website will not recognize you. You will need to log in again (if a login is required) or you must reset your templates and preferences when the website offers such functions. Then a new session cookie is generated that stores your information and which remains active until you leave the page or close your browser.

c) Permanent cookies are deleted automatically after a specified period, which can differ depending on the cookie. You can delete the cookies in your browser’s security settings at any time.

(3) For what purposes do we use cookies?  
We use cookies in order to personalize contents and advertisements, to provide social media functions and to analyse traffic to our website. In addition to that, we provide information about your use of our website to our partners for social media, advertising and and analyses. Our partners may combine this information with other data that you have provided them or which they have collected during your use of services. By continuing to use our website, you give your consent to our cookies.  
The cookies used individually and their course of action on the website can be identified using Cookiebot’s cookie manager (https://www.cookiebot.com/ ). The overview is updated on a regular basis. Below is a simplified overview.

Technically essential cookies  
Technically essential cookies allow you to use our website, by enabling basic functions like site navigation and access to secure areas of the website. Accessing our website may not work correctly without such cookies.  
_Session cookies are deleted when the browser is closed._

Performance (e.g. User’s browser) and preferences  
When using our website, cookies are implemented (e.g. to recognize the browser) in order to optimise performance (e.g. loading contents faster). If you visit our website, the country and language selection that is determined or set by you is stored in cookies in order to save you from having to select such again during subsequent visits. In advance we check whether your browser supports cookies and this information is stored in an additional cookie. You are then shown contact information that has been localized in accordance with your country and language settings and which is also stored. The legal basis in this regard is Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) f) of GDPR.  
_Session cookies – are deleted when the browser is closed._

Analytical cookies / tracking (statistics)  
We use third-party analytical cookies in order to understand how visitors use our website. This helps us to improve the quality and contents of our website. The aggregated statistical information includes data such as total number of visitors. For instance, we find out how often and in what order the individual pages are viewed and how much time the visitors spend on average on our webpages. We also learn whether Users have already visited our website at an earlier date. This is legally permitted with the consent that you have given in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) a) of GDPR. For more information, refer to Section 13 (Web analysis services).  
_Permanent cookies – remain, but are deleted automatically after a period of two years if a website has not been visited again._

Advertising cookies (Marketing)  
We use advertising cookies in order to be able to assess the effectiveness of our advertising efforts and derive any possible improvements. This is legally permitted with the consent that you have given in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) a) of GDPR.  
_Permanent cookies – remain, but are deleted automatically after a period of two years if a website has not been visited again._

(4) Control over cookies  
You can set your browser to inform you about the setting of cookies and allow cookies only in individual cases, accept cookies for certain cases or generally exclude and enable the automatic deletion of cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.  
Learn more and change your choices about the cookies we use on our dedicated page: [Paris Elysees Parfums Cookie Policy](https://paris-elysees.com/homepage/legal-notice/cookie-policy/ "Paris Elysees Parfums Cookie Policy")

6\. CONTACT FORM, GOOGLE RECAPTCHA, E-MAIL CONTACT
--------------------------------------------------

(1) Our website has a contact form, which makes it easier to contact us electronically. If a User makes use of this option, the data entered in the entry mask are sent to us and stored. The corresponding data, in particular personal data, address data and messages (free text field) can be seen directly on the respective entry mask.

At the time of submission, the following data are also stored:

The User’s IP address  
Date and time of submission of the form

(2) With regard to processing the data, reference is made to this Privacy Policy during the form submission process. Alternatively, a User may also contact us using the provided e-mail addresses. In such case, the User’s personal data sent with the e-mail will be stored. The data will be used exclusively for processing the inquiry.

(3) The processing of data that are transmitted when using the contact form or sending an e-mail is legally permitted under Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) f) of GDPR. If the objective of the e-mail contact is to get support or enquire about current customer orders or to form an agreement, the additional legal basis for data processing is Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) b) of GDPR.

(4) Personal data collected from the entry mask is used solely for the purpose of facilitating contact. Contact by e-mail also presumes the necessary legitimate interest in the processing of data. Other personal data processed during the form submission process are used to prevent a misuse of our contact form and ensure the security of our IT systems.

(5) The data will be deleted as soon as they are no longer needed to achieve the purpose for which they are collected. For the personal data collected from the entry mask of the contact form and such data that are submitted by e-mail, this is the case when the respective conversation with the User has ended. The conversation has ended when it can be inferred based on the circumstances that the respective matter has been resolved conclusively. The personal data that are additionally collected during the form submission process will be deleted at the latest after a period of seven days.

7\. E-MAIL NEWSLETTER
---------------------

### 7.1 SUBSCRIBING TO NEWSLETTER

(1) By giving your consent, you can subscribe to our e-mail newsletter (hereinafter referred to as “Newsletter”), which is sent to inform you about our products, sales and events.

(2) To register for our Newsletter subscription, we use a so-called double-opt-in process. That means that we will send an e-mail to the provided e-mail address after your registration, in which you are asked to confirm that you wish to receive our Newsletter. If you fail to confirm your registration within fourteen days, your information will be deleted automatically. In addition to that, we also store the IP addresses that you used to register and confirm as well as the times of registration and confirmation. The purpose of this process is to verify your registration and, if necessary, resolve any possible misuse of your personal data.

(3) The mandatory information required for sending the Newsletter is only your e-mail address. The provision of other information is voluntary and is used only in order to be able to address you personally. After receiving your confirmation, we save your e-mail address for the purpose of sending you the Newsletter.

(4) The aforementioned procedures during the Newsletter subscription process are legally permitted with your consent in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) a) of GDPR.

(5) Your consent to receiving our Newsletters may be revoked at any time by unsubscribing. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the respective link provided in each Newsletter e-mail or by sending an e-mail to the contact information mentioned above under 1.1 of this Privacy Policy.

(6) The data that you have provided while subscribing to our Newsletter will be deleted when you cancel your subscription.

### 7.2. NEWSLETTER TRACKING

(1) We do point out that we do analyse the behavior of Newsletter recipients. For this analysis, the sent e-mails include so-called web beacons or tracking pixels that represent single-pixel image files. For these analyses we combine data or parts thereof which are mentioned above under 2.1 of this Privacy Policy as well as the web beacons with your e-mail address and an individual ID. Even the links included in the Newsletter have this ID. With the data obtained in this manner, we create a user profile that allows us to tailor the Newsletter in order to better address the interests of our customers. In doing so, we record when you read our Newsletters, the links that you click on and thus deduce your personal interests. We in turn link such data with your actions on our website.

(2) The above tracking is legally permitted with the consent that you have given in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) a) of GDPR, provided that you have subscribed to our Newsletter.

(3)You can object to the aforementioned tracking at any time by clicking on the respective unsubscribe link provided in each Newsletter e-mail or by sending an e-mail to the contact information mentioned above under 1.1 of this Privacy Policy. The information obtained through tracking will be stored until you have unsubscribed from the Newsletter. After unsubscribing we store the data anonymously purely for statistical purposes.

(4) Tracking is moreover not possible if you have by default turned off the display of images in your e-mail client. In such case, you will not be able to see the Newsletter in its entirety and you may not be able to use all features of the Newsletter. Manually unblocking the display of images activates the above-described tracking.

### 7.3. NEWSLETTER SERVICE PROVIDER

(1) The processing operations referred to above in connection with our newsletter, and in particular the analysis and evaluation of customer information and information relating to interested parties (transaction data), are implemented with the help of the services and IT systems of the following service provider who we have commissioned as our processor:

The Rocket Science Group, LLC  
675 Ponce de Leon Ave NE Suite 5000  
Atlanta, GA 30308 USA

You can consult the page “Mailchimp and the GDPR” at this address [https://mailchimp.com/gdpr/](https://mailchimp.com/gdpr/ "Mailchimp and the GDPR")

(2) The legality is guaranteed in contracts formed in accordance with Art. 28 of GDPR and the EU standard model clauses.

8\. DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES
-------------------------------

(1) Our Newsletters are sent with the involvement of services and IT systems of an external service provider (Maichimp – The Rocket Science Group, LLC), which we have commissioned within the framework of order processing.

(2) As part of hosting our website, your data that we process will be processed by the website hosting company Infomaniak Network SA which is active on our behalf on the basis of an order processing agreement.

(3) In the case of utilizing web analytical services and third party providers, data will be transmitted within the scope described here. Third party providers participate in the Privacy Shield Agreement in accordance with Art. 45 Para. 1 of GDPR. This implies that such companies are able to demonstrate an appropriate level of data protection. For more information, see: [www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/ "Visit Privacy Shield") .

10\. AUTOMATED DECISION-MAKING
------------------------------

We do not utilise any fully automated decision-making system to justify and carry out business relations in accordance with Art. 22 of GDPR.

11\. PROFILING
--------------

In order to be able to inform and advise you about products in a targeted manner, we or services providers acting on our behalf possibly make use of web analytical services, in particular tracking technology. These facilitate an appropriate communication and advertising. In this regard, we make reference to Art. 12 Web analytical services and advertising.

12\. DATA PROCESSING BY THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS
---------------------------------------------

### 12.1 GOOGLE ANALYTICS

(1) This website uses Google Analytics, an online analytical service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics implements cookies, i.e. text files, which are saved on your computer, and which allow for analyzing your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie based on your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. If the IP anonymisation function is enabled on this website, your IP address will be abbreviated by Google beforehand within the member states of the European Union or other signatory states of European Economic Area Treaty. A full IP address is only sent in exceptional cases to a Google server in the US and truncated there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website in order to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports about website activities and offer the website operator other services linked with website use and Internet use.

(2) The IP address sent by your browser within the framework of Google Analytics is not compiled by Google with other data.

(3) You may prevent the storage of cookies by implementing the corresponding settings in your browser; please note however that you may not be able to fully utilise all the functions of this website. In addition to that, you can prevent Google from collecting data generated by the cookie and associated with your use of the website (including your IP address) and Google’s processing of such data by downloading and installing the browser plug-in provided by Google: [Analytics opt-out](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-analytics-opt-out/fllaojicojecljbmefodhfapmkghcbnh "Analytics opt-out free plugin")

(4) This website uses Google Analytics with the “\_anonymizeIp()” extension. As a result, IP addresses are only processed in a truncated form in order to prevent them from being linked to a specific person. If the data collected about you can be associated with a specific person, such data will be excluded immediately and the personal data are promptly deleted.

(5) We use Google Analytics in order to analyse and regularly improve our website. With the statistics we are able to improve our offering and make it more interesting for you as a user. For exceptional cases where personal data are sent to the US, Google has agreed to comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield, https://www.privacy-shield.gov/EU-US-Framework . The use of Google Analytics is legally permitted with the consent that you have given (Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) a) of DSGVO).

(6) Information about third party provider: Google Dublin, Google Ireland Ltd., Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland, Fax: +353 (1) 436 1001. Terms of Service: [http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html "Google Analytics Terms of Service") , Overview of privacy policy: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html "Google Analytics Privacy Policy") , and Google’s Privacy Policy: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy "Google's Privacy Policy") .

13\. SOCIAL MEDIA
-----------------

### 13.1 USE OF INSTAGRAM PLUG IN

(1) Our website makes use of so-called social plug-ins (“Plug-ins”) from Instagram, which is operated by Instagram LLC., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA (“Instagram”).

(2) When you open a page of our website that contains such a plug-in, your browser sets up a direct connection to the Instagram servers. The contents of the plug-in are sent from Instagram directly to your browser and incorporated in the web page. As a result of this integration, Instagram receives information that your browser has accessed the corresponding page of our website, even if you do not have an Instagram profile or are not currently logged into Instagram. This information (including your IP address) is sent by your browser directly to an Instagram server in the US and stored there. If you are logged into Instagram, Instagram is able to directly assign your visit to our website to your Instagram account. If you interact with the plug-ins, for instance actuating an Instagram button, this information is also directly sent to an Instagram server and stored there. The information is also posted to your Instagram account and shown to your contacts there.

(3) For information about the purpose and scope of data collection practices and further processing and use of such data by Instagram and your rights in this regard and the options available to protect your privacy, consult Instagram’s privacy policy. [https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388/](https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388/ "Instagram Privacy Policy") If you do not want Instagram to assign data collected through our website directly to your Instagram account, you must log out of Instagram prior to visiting our website. You can also prevent the loading of Instagram plug-ins by installing add-ons for your browser, e.g. the script blocker “NoScript” [http://noscript.net/](https://paris-elysees.com/homepage/legal-notice/privacy-policy/Block%20external%20scripts%20with%20NoScript "http://noscript.net/") .

14\. PLUG INS & TOOLS
---------------------

We use the following plug-ins and tools. The use of plug-ins is legally permitted under Art. 6 Para.. 1 (1) b) of GDPR.

### 14.1 YOUTUBE

(1) We have included YouTube videos in our online offering, which are stored at [https://www.youtube.com](https://www.youtube.com/ "Paris Elysees may host videos from YouTube") and can be accessed directly for viewing on our website. These are all integrated in “enhanced privacy mode”; in other words, no data is sent to YouTube about you being a user if you do not play the videos. The data mentioned under Art. 2 are sent only if you play the videos. We have no control over the transfer of these data.

(2) By visiting the website, YouTube receives information about the fact that you have accessed the corresponding sub-page of our website. In addition, the data mentioned under Art. 2 (Visiting the website) of this Statement will also be transmitted. This happens regardless of whether you have a YouTube user account that are logged into it or do not have a user account. If you are logged into Google, your data are directly assigned to your account. If you would prefer the use not to be associated with your YouTube profile, you need to log out prior to actuating the button. YouTube stores the data collected about you as usage profiles and utilises such data for advertising purposes, market research and/or to tailor its website to address requirements. Such an evaluation is carried out in particular (even for users not signed in) to provide requests-oriented advertising and to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website. You are entitled to object to the creation of such user profiles, whereas you have to contact YouTube in order to assert your objection.

(3) YouTube is a subsidiary of Google. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and their processing by YouTube, consult its privacy policy. There you will also find more information about your rights and possible settings to protect your privacy. [https://wwvv.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy](https://wwvv.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy "Google Privacy Policy") . Google also processes your personal data in the US and has agreed to comply with the EU-US-Privacy-Shield, [https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework](https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework "EU-US Privacy Shield Framework") .

### 14.2 GOOGLE FONTS

(1) This site uses so-called web fonts provided by Google to ensure the uniform presentation of fonts. When accessing a page, your browser loads the necessary web fonts into your browser cache to facilitate the correct displaying of texts and fonts.

(2) To do so, the browser you use must connect with Google’s servers. As a result of that, Google knows that our website has been accessed using your IP address. Google web fonts are used in the interests of providing a uniform and appealing presentation of our online services. This constitutes a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) f) of GDPR. If your browser does not support web fonts, your computer will use the default font. You can find more information about Google web fonts at [https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq](https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq "More information about Google Web Fonts") and in [Google’s privacy policy: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy") .

15\. YOUR RIGHTS
----------------

If personal data concerning you are processed, you are in the legal sense a person concerned by the GDPR Regulation and you have the following rights with regard to us as controller. If you wish to exercise your rights or receive more information, please contact us or our Data Security Officer: [privacy@paris-elysees.com](mailto:privacy@paris-elysees.com "Send an email to privacy@paris-elysees.com")

### A) RIGHTS ACCORDING TO ART. 15 FF. OF GDPR

(1) The Data Subject has the right to ask the Controller to confirm whether they have processed personal data relating to you; if that is the case, the Date Subject has a right to information about such personal data and to information listed in detail in Art. 15 of GDPR. Under certain legal requirements you have a right to correction in accordance with Art. 16 of GDPR, the right to restrict processing in accordance with Art. 18 of GDPR and the right to deletion (“Right to be forgotten”) in accordance with Art. 17 of GDPR. In addition, you have the right to request the receipt of data provided by you in a structured, common and machine-readable format (Right to data portability) in accordance with Art. 20 of GDPR, provided that the processing is implemented using automated procedures and based on consent under Art. 6 Para. 1 a) or Art. 9 Para. 2 a) or a contract in accordance with Art. 6 Para. 1 b) of GDPR.

### B) REVOKING CONSENT IN ACCORDANCE WITH ART. 7 PARA. 3 OF GDPR

If processing is carried out on the basis of consent, you may revoke your consent for the processing of personal data at any time. Please note that a revocation only takes effect for the future. Data processing, which took place prior to the revocation, is not affected by this.

### C) RIGHT TO LODGE A COMPLAINT

You have the option of submitting a complaint to us or to a data protection supervisory authority (Art. 77 of GDPR). The competent supervisory authority in Catalonia, Spain is: CDPA, Catalan Data Protection Authority, C/ Rosselló, 214, Esc. A, 1r 1a, 08008 Barcelona, Tel.: 93 552 78 00, Fax: 93 552 78 30, e-mail: apdcat@gencat.cat, website: [https://apdcat.gencat.cat/en/inici/](https://apdcat.gencat.cat/en/inici/ "Data Protection Authority in Catalonia, Spain")

### D) RIGHT TO OBJECT IN ACCORDANCE WITH ART. 21 OF GDPR

In addition to the aforementioned rights, you are also entitled to object as follows:

#### CASE-BASED RIGHT TO OBJECT

You have the right for reasons arising in connection with your particular situation to object at any time to the processing of personal data relating to you and based on Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) e) of GDPR (Data processing carried out for public interests) and Art. 6 Para. 1 1 f) of GDPR (Data processing for purposes of legitimate interests); this also applies to profiling based on this provision within the meaning of Art. 4 (4) of GDPR. Should you object, we will no longer process your personal data, unless we are able to provide compelling legitimate grounds for such processing that outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms or the processing serves the assertion, exercising and defense of legal claims.

#### RIGHT TO OBJECT TO PROCESSING OF DATA FOR ADVERTISING PURPOSES

In specific cases, we process your personal data for direct advertising purposes. You have the right to object at any time to the processing of personal data relating to you for the purposes of such advertising; this also applies to proﬁling, provided that it is associated with such direct advertising. If you object to processing carried out for direct advertising purposes, we will no longer process your personal data for such purposes.

16\. SECURITY
-------------

(1) We have taken technical and organisational security measures in accordance with Art. 24, 32 of GDPR in order to protect your personal data from loss, destruction, manipulation or unauthorized access. All our employees and all third parties that are involved in the data processing are obligated to comply with the requirements of GDPR and the confidential handling of personal data.

(2) SSL or TLS encryption; This site uses SSL or TSL encryption for security reasons and to protect the transmission of sensitive contents, such as orders and inquiries that you send to us as site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection by the fact that the browser’s address bar switches from “http://” to “https://” and a lock symbol appears there as well. If SSL or TSL encryption is enabled, the data that you send us cannot be read by third parties.

17\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
----------------------------------

We reserve the right to change our security and privacy protection measures if this becomes necessary due to technical development or legal changes. In such cases, we will also adjust our Privacy Policy accordingly. As a result of that, make sure that you always use the current version of our Privacy Policy.

18\. ONLINE SETTLEMENT OF DISPUTES
----------------------------------

According to the Regulation on Online Dispute Resolution in Consumer Affairs ([http://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr/](http://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr/ "Online Dispute Resolution in Consumer Affairs") ), we are obligated to inform you: We are not obligated nor willing to participate in settling a dispute in front of a consumer arbitration board.

19\. GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS
---------------------------------

This Privacy Policy supplements the General Terms and Conditions of Paris Elysees Perfumes and Beauty SL. for its website [https://paris-elysees.com/](https://paris-elysees.com/ "Paris Elysees Parfums Website") with regard to data privacy matters.

Privacy Policy updated on July 2022.  
Internal link (this website)  
External link (over the Internets)

* * *

[Women’s  
Collections](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/women-fragrances/ "Paris Elysees Collections of Fragrances for Women")

* * *

[Men’s  
Collections](https://paris-elysees.com/product-category/men-fragrances/ "Paris Elysees Collections of Fragrances for Men")

* * *

Paris  
Elysees

* * *

Your  
Account

* * *

* * *

* * *

© 2021-23 Paris Elysees Parfums | All Rights Reserved Worldwide.

### Pin It on Pinterest
